foxtheatre.org 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - The Fox Theatre

**Privacy Policy**

The Fox Theatre respects your right to privacy and your requirements to control personal information. “Personal information” includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information. The Fox Theatre does not sell any personal information.

The intent of this Privacy Statement is to inform users of our internet sites, including [**foxtheatre.org**](http://www.foxtheatre.org/) and [**FoxAtlTix.com**](http://www.foxatltix.com/) , on how the sites collect, store, and use personal information submitted via the site.

**Collection of Information**

No software or hardware techniques are employed to capture a visitor’s e-mail address without their knowledge. Certain applications on our websites may require users to register or to provide personal information in order to make a commerce transaction, to enter a contest, or to subscribe to a newsletter. Such personal information may be shared with third party organizations (these third parties may include regional arts and cultural organizations, producers, promoters, presenters, or artists) to provide a service to you as well as to assist these organizations in growing attendance.. To better enable us to service our patrons, the websites may be used as a survey tool to request demographic information. Entry of such information is optional and if you choose not to enter such information, you can successfully use these applications. If we request demographic information, we will not share your personal information as an individual with any other entity. If we do share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.

**Mailing Lists**

If you provide your e-mail address, the Fox Theatre may contact you periodically with special offers, updated information and new services. Any e-mails sent to you by the Fox Theatre offer you the option to be removed from the e-mail mailing list.

Selected applications on our web site allow visitors to subscribe to our email newsletter by providing their name and email address. If you provide the Fox Theatre with your email, mailing address or telephone number, the Fox Theatre may use this information to alert you to updated information and new services. If you wish to be removed from these mailing lists, you may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the “modify subscriptions” link in the email you received or by contacting the Fox Theatre directly. (See the ‘Contact Us’ section below).

**Information to Third Parties**

The Fox Theatre may occasionally present a special contest or promotion on its website that is sponsored by another company. To qualify for entry, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s), we will provide a statement to that effect.

**Security Used**

The Fox Theatre stores all user information in secure databases protected via a variety of access controls. Access controls include: password protection, electronic firewalls and data encryption. SSL encryption is used to protect all personal and financial information, and credit card information is not stored on a Web-enabled server. This data is accessed only for purposes specified in this privacy policy.

**Financial Information**

The Fox Theatre will protect any personal financial information that you share with us. If you make a purchase on-line, we will use your credit card number only to process your payment and will not use it for marketing purposes. For reasons of security, credit card information is not stored on our Web Server. We will retain order information for our records, but this information is never shared with third parties.

**Links**

Our sites include links to other websites whose privacy policies we do not control. Once you leave our servers (you can confirm where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you cannot find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site’s homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information. The Fox Theatre is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Cookies**

Certain applications on Fox Theatre websites invoke a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie.” We use cookies to track the progress of e-commerce transactions and to allow site users to move from one page to the next without having to re-enter personal order information. We do not share information transferred through cookies with third parties.

**Children**

We do not solicit personal information from children. Sites specifically geared toward children will not request any personal or contact information.

**Contact Us/ How to Update Your Personal Information**

You can maintain the accuracy of your personal information by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from the Fox Theatre, our partners, or selected third parties, “[ **click here to email the Fox Theatre**](mailto:boxoffice@foxtheatre.org) “: or by postal mail at:

Fox Theatre

660 Peachtree Street NE  
Atlanta, GA 30308

Please include your old and new contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections. The Fox Theatre would like to receive your comments and any questions about this policy. Please address comments or questions regarding the Fox Theatre’s privacy practices to the addresses listed above. The Fox Theatre may occasionally update this policy. Notice of revisions will be posted here.

**Disclaimer**

Under no circumstances shall the Fox Theatre, its employees, or its contractors be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive or consequential damages that may result in any way from your use or inability to use the information provided on this or any other web site supported or maintained by the Fox Theatre, or from your reliance on or use of information, services or merchandise provided on or through the web site or that result from mistakes, errors, omissions, interruptions, defects, deletion of files, delays in operation or transmission or any failure of performance. If you are dissatisfied with the information provided on this web site, or with any of the practices of the Fox Theatre in the operation of this web site, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the web site.

**TERMS OF USE:**

By using this site and/or providing us with personal information, you agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Fox Theatre, FoxAtlTix, its officers, trustees, directors, employees, successors, agents, distributors and affiliates for any and all claims, damages, losses, fees and causes of action arising from its use by you or any information or content provided by you.

The information provided on this site is for general use by its audience and all programs and artists are subject to changes without notice. Information contained on this site is presented “as is” and may contain inaccuracies and omissions. Any and all information presented on this website is done so without warranty, either expressed or implied, and any reliance on the information contained herein will be made at your own risk.

******Copyright/Ownership**

This website is owned, operated and maintained by the Fox Theatre. Unless otherwise specified, all information and content of this site, including text, logos, graphics, and images are the sole property of the Fox Theatre and may not be reproduced or used without our permission.
